http://www.erepublic.com/privacy/

Last Updated June 30, 2020
e.Republic, Inc. is the nation’s leading publishing, research, event and new media company focused on the state and local government market. Serving both government and industry for over 30 years, e.Republic publishes the market’s leading periodicals and websites, runs the largest intergovernmental conferences in the nation and produces hundreds of targeted and custom events annually. Information about e.Republic and its products and services can be obtained at www.erepublic.com.
What information does e.Republic collect?
When you visit one of our websites, we employ cookies, scripts, and tracking beacons to gather usage data such as which web pages you viewed, what website you came from, and which ads you clicked. This data remains anonymous until you register for one of our products. If we detect you are located outside the Unites States we will not collect any data, cookies, or scripts until you have clicked "I Accept" in our website prompt.
When you sign up for our products including magazines, events, webinars, papers, newsletters and books we collect personal and demographic data such as name, title, company, phone, email, address and job function.
Once you have signed up for one of our products, we collect the following:
Email behavior including what emails you opened from us and which links you clicked.
Profile data, including username and password when you login to our services.
Device and location information about your website visit including browser type and IP address.
Transactional information including billing, invoice, and payment information for current and future orders for our goods or services.
How do cookies affect you?
Cookies are small text files containing a string of characters that can be placed on your computer or mobile device that uniquely identifies your browser or device. Cookies will remain on your device until they expire or are deleted. First party cookies belong to e.Republic. Third party cookies are cookies that another party places on your device through our service to help understand how our service is being used, for example Google Analytics. We use cookies and tracking technologies in a variety of ways, including:
Keeping count of return visits to our site or our advertisers' or partners' sites; accumulating and reporting anonymous, aggregate (data collected in mass), statistical information on website and advertisement usage;
Determining which features our overall user population likes best;
Saving your password or registration data so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our sites;
Displaying the most appropriate advertising or content based on your interests.
We allow other companies that are presenting advertisements on our sites and, sometimes, in our newsletters to use tracking technology on your computer. We do not give any personally identifiable information to them as part of this relationship. Unless you visit the Web site of these companies and provide them with personally identifiable information about yourself, these tracking technologies tell those advertisers nothing about who you are. Our advertisers' use of tracking technology is subject to their own privacy policies.
You can modify your cookie settings via your internet browser (usually located within the "Help", "Tools" or "Edit" menu). Please note that if you set your browser to disable cookies or other technologies, you may not be able to access certain parts of our websites and other parts of our websites may not work properly.
How do we use this information?
Enhance the user experience on our sites. We use tracking information to determine how well each page performs overall based on aggregate user demographics and traffic patterns to those pages. This helps us continue to build a better service for you and improve our products.
Location information for displaying more relevant content or advertisements to your geography. For example, a banner ad about a California product to those in California or an email about an upcoming event near you.
Communicate with you to send email communications with information we think will be of interest to you.
Fulfillment of materials you requested including subscriptions, event materials, downloads, books and emails.
Provide measurement to help our writers and advertisers measure the effectiveness of their content and understand our audience.
Stored for backup and analysis in a CRM system (Salesforce) and cloud servers (Amazon Web Services).
How is this information shared?
Third party analytics partners for anonymous website behavior tracking. Google Analytics, Chartbeat and Google DFP (ad systems) store anonymous data about what webpages were visited, when, and in what location, what devices were used, and what advertisements were clicked.
Third party fulfillment partners for print subscription fulfillment. These companies are only allowed to use the information to help us fulfill our services to you. These third parties may not use that information for any purpose other than assisting us in providing those products and services. For example, we share your postal address with the US Postal Service to mail your print subscription to one of our magazines.
Web advertisers receive anonymous impression, click, time, and sometimes general location data about engagement with their banner ads.
We may rent your contact information, including your mailing address and phone number to third parties for marketing, merchandising or other purposes. You should presume that your personally identifiable information may thus be subject to future transactions.
You have elected to allow us to share that information at the time that you registered with us or provided us the information, or through a subsequent opt in or affirmative election through our web site. Our web forms disclose “Registration information is shared with our sponsors, and by registering you agree to receive communications from our sponsors.” Sponsors receive your name, title, company, department, phone, address, email, and data about your registration such as the date and name of the item for which you registered.
We hire third-party vendors to provide specialized services such as customer support; email message deployment; suppression, merge and de-duplication services; data processing; and special products or services that you have requested. These companies are only allowed to use the information to help us fulfill our services to you. These third parties may not use that information for any purpose other than assisting us in providing those products and services.
When required by law, such as when we respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process.
How can I manage my information?
We store personally identifiable and aggregate anonymous data until it is no longer necessary to provide products related to that data. California Residents: You may request a copy of your data, opt out of the sale of your data, or request that we delete your data here.
Users who would rather not provide any of the user data requested by any of our registration or subscription processes do not need to register with us or to subscribe. You can still view much of the content and use many of the services offered by our sites without registering. Opting not to provide certain personal information when requested means that you may not be able to access some areas of our web site.
Changes to this Web Site Privacy Statement
If we decide to change this Web Site Privacy Statement, we will post the revised policy at this location, so that users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use Personal Information in a manner that is substantially different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will seek to notify users by way of an email.
Contact Information
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at subscriptions@erepublic.com.
